

# IAN B. RAMOS

Video Editor

# **CAREER SUMMARY**

Coordinate graphic design projects from concept through completion. Work closely with clients to create vision, conceive designs, and consistently meet deadlines and requirements. Effectively build, motivate, and direct design and production teams. Coordinate freelance designers, consultants and vendors to meet all project requirements. Create and conduct highly persuasive sales and marketing presentations. Expertly convert features to benefits to achieve client objectives.

# **SKILLS**

Auto Cad Photoshop Video Editing (Filmora, Adobe Premier, Cupcat) Microsoft Office Data Entry Documentation

## **EDUCATION**

# **Aces Tagum College**

Information Technology 2003 – 2006

# Korhphil Tesda Vocational School

Computer Hardware Servicing 2008-2010

# CONTACT

Phone Number:

+63 9557953077 (Globe)

+63 991-354-1898 (DITO)

Whats app:

+63 9557953077

Skype ID:

live:.cid.ce0c7a5a871fc0ab

**Email Address:** 

ianramos9114@gmail.com

FB Profile:

https://www.facebook.com/iamin911

### **CHARACTER REFERENCES:**

### Ledjie Adlawan

Executive VA – Amazon VA +63467400289

ledjiecabugatan@gmail.com

### **CHRISTOPER CAINOY**

Sales & Marketing Manager <u>Jenson Land & Realty Dev't Corp.</u> +639338505644

christopermabantacainoy@gmail.com

### **ANNABELLE OPAMIN**

<u>CPA</u>

Into-OPamin CPA's and Company +639338501752

opaminacctg@gmail.com

### **RHAYFIEL SINAMAO**

Civil Engineer DPWH Region XI +639257616236 sinamaorhayfeil@yahoo.com

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **EPC INTEGRITY**

 Subcon of the local Telecom company such as DITO,GLOBE, SMART.

### April 2020 - August 31, 2022

Duties and Responsibilities:

We design tower from our client DITO such as Greenfield and IBS Project and documentations.

### Jezka Construction

- Subcon of the local Telecom company suh as DITO,GLOBE, SMART

### Febuary 2017 - March 2020

Duties and Responsibilities:

We design tower from our client DITO such as Greenfield and IBS Project and documentations.

### Pc Quickbuys 2010-2013

Duties and Responsibilities:

Computer Sales and Repair

Computer Reformat and installation

Installation any Kind of Software Games and Etc

Technical support for both software and hardware problems.

Network and Internet network maintenance

### TRAININGS AND SEMINARS

### National Certificate NC2

Computer Hardware and Servicing

### **Certificate of Completion**

Adobe Premier Pro Masterclass